Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advertisements, 1932-1995
  - Oversized Materials
    - Allied Chemical
      - 1964-1968, Consumer newspaper (Box OV1)
      - 1966, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1967, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1968, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1969, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1970-1971, magazine (Box OV1)
    - American Express
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1952-1961, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1955-1958, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1958-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box OV1)
      - 1959-1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
    - American Motors
      - 1965-1967, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1965-1966, Consumer newspaper (Box OV1)
      - 1966, Consumer and trade magazine (Kelvinator) (Box OV1)
      - 1967, Consumer newspaper (Box OV1)
    - American Safety Razor (ASR)
      - 1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1961, Consumer newspaper (Box OV1)
    - AMF, Inc.
      - 1979, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1980, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
    - AMK Corporation (United Fruit products)
      - 1970, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
    - Arnold Bakers
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
    - Association of American Railroads
      - 1955-1957, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
    - AVCO Manufacturing Corp.
      - 1952-1957, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV2)
      - 1958-1964, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV2)
      - 1959-1965, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV2)
      - 1962-1965, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV2)
    - AVCO-Crosley Consumer Products
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV2)
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (refrigerators) (Box OV2)
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (televisions) (Box OV2)
      - 1949, Consumer newspaper (televisions) (Box OV2)
      - 1949-1951, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box OV2)
      - 1949-1952, Consumer newspaper (refrigerators) (Box OV2)
      - 1949-1953, Consumer newspaper (ranges) (Box OV2)
      - 1949-1954, Consumer magazine (ranges) (Box OV2)
      - 1950, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV2)
      - 1950, Consumer magazine (televisions) (Box OV2)
      - 1950, Consumer newspaper (televisions) (Box OV2)
      - 1950-1952, Consumer magazine (refrigerators) (Box OV2)
      - 1951, Consumer magazine (televisions) (Box OV2)
      - 1951, Consumer newspaper (televisions), 2 folders (Box OV2)
      - 1951-1952, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV2)
      - 1951-1954, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box OV2)
      - 1952-1953, Consumer magazine (air conditioners) (Box OV2)
      - 1952-1953, Trade magazine (air conditioners) (Box OV2)
      - 1953, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV2)
      - 1953, Consumer magazine (washer/dryer) (Box OV2)
      - 1953-1955, Consumer magazine (refrigerators) (Box OV2)
      - 1953-1955, Consumer newspaper (refrigerators) (Box OV2)
      - 1954, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV3)
      - 1954, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box OV3)
      - 1955, Consumer promotional items (Box OV3)
    - Avis
      - 1969-1972, Consumer magazine (Box OV3)
      - 1969-1972, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
    - Beck Shoe Store
      - 1970, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
    - Beech-Nut
      - 1964-1967, Consumer magazine (Box OV3)
    - Benton and Bowles
      - 1938-1939, Trade magazine (Box OV3)
      - 1952-1969, Trade magazine (Box OV3)
      - 1957-1958, Trade magazine (Box OV3)
      - 1959-1961, Trade newspaper (Box OV3)
      - 1962-1966, Trade magazine (Box OV3)
      - 1967-1971, Trade magazine (Box OV3)
      - 1974, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
    - Best Foods
      - Corporate and multiple product
        - 1934-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
      - Hellmann's Mayonnaise
        - 1933, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
        - 1934, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box OV3)
        - 1935-1939, Consumer magazine (Box OV3)
        - 1936-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
        - 1945-1951, Consumer magazine (Box OV3)
      - Nucoa oleomargarine
        - 1934-1936, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
        - 1936-1951, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV3)
        - 1943-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box OV3)
      - Standard Milling
        - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
      - Various condiments
        - 1951, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
      - Various shoe polish
        - 1939, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV4)
    - Bituminous Coal Institute
      - 1945-1949, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1950, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
    - Bristol-Myers
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Sal Hepatica) (Box OV4)
    - Burlington Industries (Klopman Mills)
      - 1970, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
    - Caltex Petroleum Corporation
      - 1970, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
      - 1971, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
    - Calvert Distillers Corporation
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box OV4)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box OV4)
      - 1938-1939, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV4)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box OV4)
      - 1960, Consumer magazine (Calvert Gin) (Box OV4)
      - 1960, Consumer newspaper (Calvert Gin) (Box OV4)
    - Canada Dry Corporation
      - 1967, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
    - Can Manufacturers' Institute
      - 1944, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1945-1948, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
    - Carling Brewing Company
      - 1950-1958, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1951-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
      - 1952-1959, Trade magazine (Box OV4)
    - Champion International Corporation
      - 1972, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
      - 1973, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
    - Chemical Bank/New York Trust Company
      - 1960-1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1961-1966, Consumer newspaper (Box OV4)
      - 1962-1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1964-1965, Consumer magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1966-1967, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1967-1968, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV4)
      - 1968-1972, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV4)
      - 1969-1974, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV4)
      - Undated, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV4)
    - Cigar Institute of America
      - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box OV5)
    - Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Company
      - Corporate and Multiple Product
        - 1935, Trade magazine (Box OV5)
        - 1935-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
        - 1937-1940, Trade newspaper (Box OV5)
      - Colgate dental creme and powder
        - 1935, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - Palmolive soap
        - 1936, Consumer magazine (Box OV5)
        - 1936-1937, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - Super Suds
        - 1936, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
        - 1936-1940, Trade magazine (Box OV5)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System
      - 1940-1945, Consumer magazine (Box OV5)
      - 1941-1942, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
    - Consolidated Food Corporation
      - 1973-1976, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1974, Trade magazine (Box OV5)
    - Continental Airlines
      - 1974, Consumer magazine (Box OV5)
    - Continental Baking Company
      - 1932, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box OV5)
      - 1937-1938, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box OV5)
      - 1938-1939, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
    - Continental Oil Company (CONOCO)
      - 1953, Consumer magazine (Box OV5)
      - 1953, Consumer newspaper (Box OV5)
      - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box OV6)
      - 1954, Consumer newspaper (Box OV6)
      - 1955, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box OV6)
      - 1955, Consumer newspaper (Box OV6)
      - 1955-1958, Trade magazine (Box OV6)
      - 1956, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box OV6)
      - 1956, Consumer newspaper (Box OV6)
      - 1957, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box OV6)
      - 1957-1960, Consumer newspaper (Box OV6)
      - 1958-1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV6)
      - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box OV6)
    - Crowell-Collier Publishing Company
      - 1943-1944, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1943-1944, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
      - 1945-1946, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1945-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
      - 1947, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1947-1951, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV7)
      - 1948, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1949-1951, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV7)
    - Crum and Forster
      - 1972-1973, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
      - 1973, Trade magazine (Box OV7)
    - Dana Perfumes
      - 1972, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
    - Diamond Match Company
      - 1951-1953, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1951-1956, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
    - Digital Equipment Corporation
      - 1980, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
    - Dr. Pepper Company
      - 1941, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
    - Ed Dalton
      - 1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
    - E.F. Hutton and Company
      - 1971, Trade magazine (Box OV7)
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons
      - 1963-1964, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV7)
      - 1964, Consumer newspaper (Vigran) (Box OV7)
      - 1965-1967, Consumer newspaper (Sweeta) (Box OV7)
    - Fiat Motors of North America
      - 1978-1979, Consumer magazine (corporate) (Box OV7)
      - 1979, Consumer magazine (Strada) (Box OV7)
      - 1979, Consumer magazine (128 sedan) (Box OV7)
    - Fitgers Brewing Company (Fitzger's beer)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
    - Florida Citrus Commission
      - 1943-1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1943-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box OV7)
      - 1944-1962, Trade newspaper (Box OV7)
      - 1945-1949, Trade magazine (Box OV7)
      - 1950-1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV8)
      - 1950-1963, Trade magazine (Box OV8)
      - 1959-1960, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
      - 1960-1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV8)
      - 1961-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
    - General Aniline and Film Corporation (Ansco)
      - 1957-1960, Consumer magazine (Box OV8)
    - General Electric
      - 1950-1956, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
      - 1951, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
    - General Foods
      - Corporate and Multiple Product
        - 1933-1941, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
        - 1938-1963, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV8)
        - 1951-1964, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
      - Birds Eye frozen foods
        - 1959-1971, Consumer magazine (Box OV8)
        - 1960-1971, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
      - Certo and Sure Jell
        - 1938-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
        - 1950-1954, Consumer magazine (Box OV8)
      - Diamond Crystal Salt
        - 1936-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
      - Gaines dog food
        - 1952-1957, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
        - 1953-1961, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV8)
        - 1959-1973, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
      - Jell-O products
        - 1937-1959, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
      - Log Cabin syrup
        - 1938-1954, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV8)
        - 1951-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
      - Maxwell House
        - 1935-1936, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
        - 1937-1938, Consumer newspaper (Box OV8)
        - 1937-1939, Trade magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1941, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1943, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1945-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1948-1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1948-1949, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1950, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1951, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1952, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1952-1954, Consumer magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1953-1954, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1955-1957, Consumer magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1955-1958, Consumer newspaper (Box OV9)
        - 1958-1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV9)
        - 1959-1961, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1960-1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1960-1961, Trade magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1960-1961, Trade newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1962-1963, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1963-1967, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1964-1967, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
      - Post cereals
        - 1932-1934, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1932-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1935-1959, Trade magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1937-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1941-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1948-1954, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1949-1956, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1957-1964, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1957-1967, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1966-1974, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1945-1949, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1952, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
      - Walter Baker chocolates
        - 1937-1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV10)
        - 1945-1949, Consumer newspaper (Box OV10)
        - 1953, Consumer (Box OV10)
      - Yuban coffee
        - 1953-1958, Consumer magazine (Box OV11)
        - 1953-1960, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
        - 1959, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
        - 1960, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
        - 1960-1963, Trade magazine (Box OV11)
        - 1961-1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV11)
        - 1961-1963, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV11)
      - Other coffee
        - Bliss
          - 1956-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
        - Brim
          - 1970, Consumer magazine (Box OV11)
          - 1970-1978, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
      - Other products
        - Carnation Instant Breakfast
          - 1969, Consumer magazine (Box OV11)
        - Wheaties, Gold Medal flour
          - 1943, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
        - Wigwam syrup
          - 1953, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
          - 1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV11)
    - Gillette
      - 1970-1971, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV11)
    - Glass Container Manufacturer's Institute
      - 1960-1965, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV11)
    - GMF Robotics
      - 1986, Trade magazine (Box OV11)
    - Hanes Corporation (L'Erin cosmetics)
      - 1977-1978, Consumer magazine (Box OV11)
    - Hardee's Food System
      - 1975-1976, Consumer newspaper (Box OV11)
    - Hasbro Industries
      - 1971-1972, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box OV11)
    - Heublein Incorporated
      - 1953-1955, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box OV11)
      - 1963, Trade magazine (Bell's) (Box OV11)
    - Holland-America Cruises
      - 1977-1978, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV11)
      - 1979-1980, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV11)
    - Hy-Gain Electronics (CB radio)
      - 1977, Trade magazine (Box OV11)
    - International Business Machines (IBM)
      - 1954-1955, newspaper (Box OV11)
      - 1955, magazine (Box OV11)
      - 1956, magazine (Box OV11)
      - 1956, newspaper (Box OV11)
      - 1957, magazine (Box OV11)
      - 1957-1958, newspaper (Box OV11)
      - 1958, magazine, 2 folders (Box OV11)
      - 1959, magazine, 3 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1959-1961, newspaper (Box OV12)
      - 1960, magazine, 2 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1961, magazine, 2 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1962, magazine, 3 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1963, magazine, 2 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1963-1965, newspaper (Box OV12)
      - 1964, magazine (Box OV12)
      - 1965, magazine (Box OV12)
      - 1966-1967, magazine (Box OV12)
      - 1966-1967, newspaper (Box OV12)
    - Kentile
      - 1958-1970, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV12)
    - Lenox China
      - 1949-1953, Consumer magazine (Box OV12)
      - 1952-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box OV12)
    - Lorillard Corporation (Kent)
      - 1964, Consumer newspaper (Box OV12)
    - M&R Brand Dietetics Laboratories
      - 1953-1960, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV12)
      - 1953-1962, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV12)
    - Marine Midland Bank
      - 1976-1980, Consumer newspaper (Box OV12)
      - 1977-1978, Consumer magazine (Box OV12)
    - McKesson and Robbins
      - 1957, Trade magazine (Box OV12)
    - Medicus
      - 1978, Trade magazine (Box OV12)
    - Muscular Dystrophy Association
      - 1973, Consumer newspaper (Box OV12)
    - Mutual of New York
      - 1952-1957, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1953-1965, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV13)
      - 1960-1965, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV13)
    - National Association of Manufacturers
      - 1946-1947, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1946-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
    - National Distillers Products
      - 1934-1954, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1940-1954, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
      - 1955, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1955-1956, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
      - 1956, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
    - New York World's Fair
      - 1964-1965, Trade magazine (Box OV13)
    - Norwich-Pharmacal Company
      - 1956, Trade magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1959-1962, magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1959-1964, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
    - Parker Pen Company
      - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
    - P. Ballantine and Sons
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
    - Peter Paul Incorporated
      - 1970, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
    - Philip Morris
      - 1952-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
      - 1953-1957, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1958, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1958-1961, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
      - 1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
      - 1962-1963, Consumer newspaper (Box OV13)
      - 1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV13)
    - Pitney Bowes
      - Undated, Trade magazine (Box OV13)
    - Procter & Gamble
      - Corporate and multiple product
        - 1959, Consumer magazine (Canada) (Box OV14)
        - 1974-1979, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
      - Bonus
        - 1965, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
      - Bounce
        - 1972-1975, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
      - Charmin
        - 1968-1979, Consumer (Box OV14)
      - Crest
        - 1955-1958, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1956-1961, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
        - 1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1962-1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1963-1976, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
        - 1964-1966, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1967-1970, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
      - Hidden Magic
        - 1959, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
      - Ivory Snow
        - 1944-1945, Consumer (Box OV14)
      - Pampers
        - 1962-1964, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
        - 1962-1972, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1969-1973, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV14)
      - Pin-It
        - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
      - Prell
        - 1946, Trade newspaper (Box OV14)
        - 1948-1951, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV14)
      - Rely
        - 1973-1975, Consumer (Box OV14)
      - Scope
        - 1965-1978, Consumer (Box OV14)
      - Stardust
        - 1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1961, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
      - Tide
        - 1946, Consumer newspaper (Box OV14)
        - 1948, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box OV14)
        - 1948-1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1950, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box OV14)
        - 1950-1951, Consumer magazine (Box OV14)
        - 1951, Consumer newspaper, 4 folders (Box OV14)
        - 1952, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
        - 1952-1953, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
        - 1952-1957, Trade newspaper (Box OV15)
        - 1953, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box OV15)
        - 1953-1954, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
        - 1954, Trade magazine (Box OV15)
        - 1954-1955, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
        - 1955, Trade magazine (Box OV15)
        - 1955-1957, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
        - 1956, Trade magazine (Box OV15)
        - 1956-1958, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
      - Whirl
        - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
      - Zest
        - 1952-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
        - 1957-1958, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
    - Prudential Insurance Company of America
      - 1940, Trade magazine (Box OV15)
    - Railway Express Agency
      - 1955-1962, Trade magazine (Box OV15)
      - 1960-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
    - Richardson-Vick
      - 1966, Trade magazine (Box OV15)
      - 1967-1968, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
    - Savings Bank Association of the State of New York
      - 1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
    - Schenley Ind. Incorporated
      - 1948, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV15)
      - 1948, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV15)
    - Schick
      - 1957-1959, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV15)
      - 1958-1961, Consumer newspaper (Box OV15)
      - 1960-1961, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
    - S.C. Johnson
      - 1956-1961, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV15)
      - 1956-1973, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV15)
    - Schlitz
      - 1980, Consumer magazine (Box OV15)
    - Showtime/The Movie Channel
      - 1982-1984, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV16)
    - Shulton
      - 1963-1967, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1965-1967, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1966, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
    - Studebaker-Packard
      - 1955-1956, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1955-1956, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1955-1957, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV16)
      - 1956, Trade magazine (Box OV16)
    - Texaco
      - 1961-1965, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
      - 1962-1963, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1964-1966, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1966-1970, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
      - 1967-1980, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1971-1980, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
    - This Week Magazine
      - 1954-1957, Trade magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1954-1957, Trade newspaper (Box OV16)
    - Time Incorporated
      - 1949-1950, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
    - UNICEF
      - 1971-1979, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
    - Unicom Group of Insurance Company
      - 1973, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
    - United Fund of Westchester
      - 1967, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
    - United States Rubber Company
      - 1966, Trade magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1966, Trade newspaper (Box OV16)
    - United States Treasury Department
      - 1983, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
    - Upholstery Leather Group Incorporated
      - 1957, Trade magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1957, Trade newspaper (Box OV16)
    - Warner-Lambert Pharmaceutical
      - 1941, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
    - West End Brewery
      - 1965-1966, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1965-1966, Consumer newspaper (Box OV16)
    - Western Electric
      - 1946, Trade newspaper (Box OV16)
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box OV16)
      - 1956-1963, Consumer and trade magazine (Box OV16)